你觉得我们还该让他重新嗑药吗
You think we're gonna get him back on those meds again?
这些是给蒲伯的吗
Are those for Pope?
我们昨晚来的时候我就在欣赏这个小宝贝儿了
I was admiring this little gem when we came in tonight.
所以这东西能开多快 大概120码 还是130码
So what's this thing do? About a buck 20? A buck 30?
-开阔的路 我开过140码 -哇哦
- Open road, I've done 140. - Wow.
好吧 我真的蛮喜欢你爸 他看起来很酷
Well, I really liked your dad. He seems very cool.
-和那一盘钱的故事 老兄
- And that pallet of money story, man...
-那太疯狂了
that was crazy.
有一天 我动他的公文包 他就生气了
The other day, he freaked when I moved his briefcase.
他所有的机密文件和别的鬼东西
All his classified documents and shit?
和你外婆一起住怎么样
How's living with your grandmother?
还可以
It's okay.
那有很多人要对付啊
That's a lot of people to contend with
-和之前只有你和你妈住相比 -是啊
- after just being you and your Mom. - Yeah.
嗨 老妈
Hi, Mom.
嗨 宝贝儿
Hi, baby.
莲
Renn?
该死 嘿
Shit. Hey. Hey! Hey.
你干得好 你让J对他的家庭敞开心扉了
You did good. You got J opening up about his family.
她坚定地盯着你
#She stares deeply #
封锁在身体内
#Locked inside me #
熊熊地燃烧
#Burnin' brightly #
他们中有人知道我无法承受
#One they know that I cannot take #
等待一切开始
#Waitin' for it all to begin #
每一晚 他们都占上风
#Every night now, they'll win #
来见见我的大黑洞
#Come and meet my black hole #
有个大黑洞
#Got a big black hole #
我有个大黑洞
#I've got a big black hole #
我有个大黑洞 大黑洞
#I've got a big black, big black hole #
我身体内蕴含了一个大黑洞
#Got a big black hole inside of me #
有一个
#Got a #
我现在开到120码了
I'm doing 120 right now!
拿出点大人的样子 看着吧
Put on your big boy pants, man! Let's see it!
－125码 130码
- 125! 130!
-用最快速度 来吧 -别 别 别
- Floor it! Come on! - No, no, no.
我做不到
I couldn't do it!
哇 比做爱爽吧 哈
Whoo. Better than sex, huh?
更像心脏病发作
More like a heart attack.
还想来一次吗 走起
Wanna go again? Go!
得看到如果这些家伙在不在这 我有点 呃
Need to see if these guys are in here. I've got, uh...
我是来找我儿子的 安德鲁・科迪
I'm here for my son, Andrew Cody.
我被告知你是他的假释官
I was told you were his parole officer.
你能让我知道他为什么被捕吗
You want to let me know why he was arrested?
闪押 只是警告
Flash incarceration. A warning.
如果他再违反了假释条例
If he violates his parole again,
他剩下的刑期就会在监狱里过了
he'll serve out the rest of his sentence in prison.
我儿子没有违反假释条例
My son did not violate his parole.
我儿子有工作 有房子 他还定期向你汇报
My son has a job, a home, and he reports to you regularly.
也许我该给我的律师打电话
Maybe I should just call my lawyer.
你想浪费钱的话 请自便
You wanna waste your money, you go ahead.
没通过的毒品测试他也无能为力
There's nothing he can do about a failed drug test.
-安德鲁没有吸毒
- Andrew does not take drugs.
好吧 他肯定有嗑过什么
Well, he must've taken something.
他又开始嗑药了吗
Is he back on his meds?
坐下
Sit down.
他很快就会被释放了
He'll be released shortly.
如有再犯 他就真的要服刑
Happens again, he'll do real time.
-这些需要盖章 -好的
- I need those checked out. - All right.
我在为上大学存钱 给尼基
I'm saving up for college, for Nicky,
如果她要上的话
if she ever goes.
上帝知道现在大学不是排着队
Lord knows schools aren't lining up
-录取全C的学生［换算为百分制约为70区间段］
- to admit "C" Students right now.
噢 她会进步的 她是个聪明的孩子
Oh, she'll get it together. She's a smart kid.
噢 你就放那吧 老兄 我会锁起来的
Oh, you can leave it in there, man. I-I'll lock it.
噢不用了 没事
Oh, no, no, no. That's okay.
我爸想知道你要吃墨西哥菜还是意大利菜
My dad wants to know if you want Mexican or Italian.
都可以
Whatever's fine.
我不知道哪个更糟糕
I don't know what's worse...
他讨厌你还是请你来家庭之夜
him hating you or inviting you for family night.
等等
Oh, wait.
你打扮越性感 安德森给我们卷子打分的时候
The hotter you look, the better mood Anderson'll be
心情就越好
when she grades our tests.
－恩
- Mm.
坐下吧 大家
Sit down, everyone.
安德森小姐出门了 我来监考
Ms. Anderson is out. I'm giving the test.
看来这次到我了
Looks like it's my turn.
你觉得他会给我任何答案吗
Think he'll give me any of the answers?
-恩 -嗯哼
- Mm. - Mm-hmm.
往后传
Pass it back.
洗个澡 带上你的监听器 去学校
Take a shower, put on your wire, go to school.
-他信任我 -很好
- He trusts me. - Good.
听着 我做不到 我 我都睡不着
Look, I can't do this. I can't... I can't even sleep.
你决定跟卧底警察买5斤海洛因的时候
Where was this conscience when you decided
这种良心去哪了
to buy 5 grams of heroin from an undercover cop?
-我从没干过这种事 好吧 -我需要细节
- I've never done this before, okay? - I need details...
科迪一家做了什么 他们下一步要怎么做
what the Codys did, what they're doing next.
我该说什么
What am I supposed to say?
讲真吗 我该说什么啊
Seriously? What am I supposed to say?
"嗨 J 最近怎么样
"Hey, J, how's it going?
噢 对了 你家里人最近在犯什么事儿啊”
By the way, what crimes have your family been up to lately?"
我是唯一一个保证你生活不翻天的人
I'm the only thing keeping your life from blowing up.
你该谢我
You should be thanking me.
你得感谢我
谢谢
Thank you.
把鞋子穿上
Put your shoes on.
我有东西给你看
I'm gonna show you something.
我需要点建议
I need some advice.
你女儿尖叫不停的时候你怎么办
What do you do when your daughter's screaming nonstop
因为你不让她打耳洞
because you won't let her get her ears pierced?
-我说 你会怎么做 -她多大了
- I mean, what do you do? - How old is she?
6岁
6.
但她妈会吃固态食物前就打了耳洞
But her mother's were pierced before she was on solids.
这是某种拉丁习俗 我不懂
It's a Latina thing. I don't know.
-你 我的朋友 遭殃了
- You, my friend, are screwed.
-好吗 就接受了吧
-All right? So just accept it.
举白旗然后 然后就 你懂的
Raise up that white flag and... and just, you know,
-别乱耍脾气 -好
- avoid all the tantrums. - Yeah.
集中精力在家族生意上 我就想说这个
Focus on the family business. That's what I say.
事情进展怎么样了
How's that going, anyway?
很好 是的 很好
It's good. Yeah, it's good.
我是说 总比和别人合作强
I mean, it's better than working for someone else.
我花了两年
I spent two years keeping
让这些书不落到精英铂金资产手里
the books for Elite Platinum Properties.
基本上就是给有个酷炫的名字叫阿蒂的白痴
Basically just a fancy name for a shithead named Artie.
我跟你说
- I'm telling you,
在他打高尔夫的时候我帮他打理生意
I kept his business running while he made his tee time.
我应该成为合伙人的
I deserved to be partner.
我要的就是加薪 他说他不能决定
All I asked for was a raise, said he couldn't justify it.
-你会怎么办 -嗯 我等到报税的时候
- What'd you do? - Well, I waited till tax time,
然后我会扔全年份的发票在他桌上
then I dumped a year's worth of invoices on his desk.
刚开始 他吓尿了 后来他 呃
First, he shit a brick. Then he, uh...
他求我留下来
- ...then he begged me to stay.
你怎么说
What'd you say?
我说 我不能决定啊
Well, I said, I couldn't justify it.
干杯
- Cheers.
那你呢
What about you?
你有没有想给你老板竖根中指过
You ever feel like giving your boss the finger?
-谁没有过 -就是
- Who hasn't? - Yeah.
你会怎么做
What would you do?
你懂得 要报复他 你会怎么做啊
You know, to get back at him. What would you do?
来嘛 告诉我说你想都没想过
Come on. Tell me you haven't thought about it.
-这就是扯淡吧 -两瓶啤酒
- I call bullshit. - Two beers?
-你们的
- Here you go.
-谢谢你 -谢谢
- Thank you. - Thanks.
可能我会 呃 调整文件
Maybe I would, uh, adjust the paperwork,
然后让罗纳德里根号［一艘核动力舰艇］上的ATM机都
so all the ATMs on the U.S.S Ronald Reagan
在他们部署三个月的时间里
would run out of cash
都没现金可以取
about three months into their deployment.
是吧
- Right?
我要藏起 我会藏起所有漏洞
I'd bury... I would bury all the shortcomings
然后让这看起来完全无踪可循
and I'd make it completely untraceable.
呃 但你不会惹祸上身吗
Ah. But wouldn't that get you in trouble?
做好了就不会
Not if I did it right.
有钱能使鬼推磨
Shit would roll uphill with that kind of money.
你能让这么多钱消失吗
You could make that much money go missing?
你在逗我吗
Are you kidding me?
那种钱整天都在消失
That kind of money goes missing all the time.
海军只是不想让任何人知道
The Navy just doesn't want anybody to know about it.
致幻剂
Lsd.
一定哪里出了错
There must've been some mistake.
我是这么跟保释官说的
That's what I told my P.O.
我这辈子都没嗑过那玩意
I've never taken that shit in my life.
-你确定没有人搞小动作吗 -不 没问题
- Are you sure this wasn't a shakedown? - No, he's straight.
"尿检不会说谎" 他是这么说的
"Piss test don't lie." That's what he said.
好吧 这不是真的
Well, that's not true.
他们整天把样本搞乱
They mix up those samples all the time.
他们要我再测一次
They made me take a second test.
结果是阳性
- It's positive.
-是巴斯 他要见我们
- That's Baz. He wants to meet.
-他一直在研究一个主意
-He's been working on an idea.
你来吗
You comin'?
那里原先有栋房子
Used to be a house down there.
埃米利奥和卡门・欧提兹住的
Emilio and Carmen Ortiz.
我在巡逻队时一起工作过
Used to work with me back when I was on patrol.
条子吗
Cops?
秘密线人
Confidential informants.
他们在沿海有过一系列抢劫
They had done a string of robberies along the coast
后来想洗手不干
and wanted out.
我觉得他们蹲点牢子就没事了
I think they would've been okay after they did a little time,
-但是
- but...
-他们犯了惹上
-...they made the mistake of getting into business
亚尼内・科迪的错
- with Janine Cody.
-J的外婆
-J's grandmother.
她怀疑他们是线人
She suspected they were informants,
派她儿子安德鲁烧了那房子
sent her son Andrew to burn the house down.
他们在这找到了卡门
They found Carmen here.
她还算走运 在她的皮肤开始烧毁脱落前
She was lucky. She died of smoke inhalation
死于吸入烟尘过多
before her skin started to burn off.
我们后来把牙齿送到实验室才能确认是她
Could only confirm it was her after we sent the teeth to the lab.
而埃米利奥... 他肯定试着跑了
And Emilio... he must've tried to run.
在门边找到了他
Found him by the door.
部分燃烧的屋顶掉下来 砸到他的躯干
Part of the burning ceiling fell, severed his torso.
1997年 三月三号
March 3, 1997.
所以最后能给你提供关于科迪一家消息的人
So the last people to inform on the Codys for you
被烧死了
burned to death.
而你想让我叫J去做一样的事
And you want me to get J to do the same thing?
他不是他们中的一份子 不完全是
He's not one of them. Not really.
这就是他们怎么对局外人
And this is what they do to outsiders.
唯一保护他的方法就是让他远离他们
Only way to protect him is to get him away from them.
但要怎么做
But how?
继续你一直在做的事
Keep doing what you're doing.
他亲了我
He kissed me.
给他发信息
Text him.
问他放学后要干嘛
See what he's doing after school.
你是叫我睡一个17岁小孩儿吗
Are you asking me to sleep with a 17-year-old kid?
当然不是 那会犯法的
Of course not. That would be illegal.
但如果你在乎那孩子 在我们要验牙齿
But if you care about that kid, get him out,
确认他身份前 救他出来
before we have to ID him by his teeth.
你 在对我保守秘密吗
You, uh, holding out on me?
我没有嗑药
I didn't do LSD.
-嘿 你吃了个百吉饼吗 -什么
- Hey, you eat a bagel? - What?
-百吉饼 你有吃吗
- A bagel. Did you eat a bagel?
-你他妈在说什么啊
- What the hell are you talking about?
罂粟种子 老兄 你的尿里有那玩意儿
The poppy seeds, man. That shit is in your piss.
-每个人都知道 -别这样
- Everybody knows that. - Come on.
那是鸦片 蠢货
That's opium, dipshit.
噢对 那可能是别的什么
Yeah, well, maybe something else.
可能不是鸦片 但 你懂的
Maybe not the poppies, but, you know,
差不多的东西 我就说说
something like that. Just sayin'.
为了你的健康
To your health.
嘿
Hey.
蒲伯在监狱呆了一晚上
Pope spent the night in jail.
是 我听说了
Yeah, I heard.
一晚上还不够把牙刷做成小刀呢
Not even long enough to make a toothbrush into a shiv.
好了 开始吧 -我觉得我有些
Okay, let's get started. - I think I have something.
大料
Could be big.
彭德顿营地
Camp Pendleton.
-哇哦 这怎么了 -我们要突袭那
- Wow, what about it? - We're gonna hit it.
这是个军事基地
That's a military base.
听起来不错 我干
Sounds awesome. I'm in.
耶 我们要去干嘛 核弹头还是坦克
Yeah, what are we going for? A nuclear warhead or a tank?
那基地里有一大笔钱 一大笔
There is a ton of cash on that base. A ton.
被配狙击来福枪的士兵和攻击直升机围着
Surrounded by soldiers with sniper rifles and attack helicopters.
但如果他们不知道我们要去偷 那些全都没用
Yeah, all useless if they don't know we're taking it.
怎么搞
How?
还在想呢
Still working on that part.
噢 听起来万无一失啊
Well, sounds like a foolproof plan.
听着 这需要点时间
Look, it's gonna take some time,
但我的线人知道怎么出入那个基地
but my mark knows the ins and outs of the base.
-等等 你的线人 -对啊 保罗
- Wait, your mark? - Yeah. Paul.
尼基她爸
Nicky's dad.
尼基 J的女朋友尼基
Nicky? J's girlfriend Nicky?
对啊 他管着长期部署的航空母舰上的经费
Yeah. He handles serious money for long deployments,
我在努力动员他
aircraft carriers, all that. I've been workin' him hard.
等等 我们什么时候开始和
Hold on. Since when do we do jobs with people
外面的人一起干活了
outside of the family?
这个叫保罗的家伙 听起来像个孬种
This Paul guy... he sounds like a pussy.
还有 条子一察觉到他的踪迹
And the... the second the cops breathe in his direction,
他就会指向我们
he's going to point them right to us.
蒲伯 我能应付他
Pope, I can handle him.
我觉得他准备好要越界了 他想要着呢
I got a feeling he's ready to cross a line. He wants it.
-他只需要有人推他一把 我跟你说 -不要
- He just needs a push. I'm telling you... - No.
不 不 不
No! No! No.
我们联合起来 带枪进去
We case a joint, we go in with guns,
带钱出来
we come out with cash.
没那么复杂
It's not that complicated.
就像抢富国银行那次吗 简单到你进了监狱
Like the Wells Fargo job? So easy it landed you in prison.
对 为了救你
Yeah. Saving your ass.
你也要干这狗屁事吗
Are you on board with this crap?
看看这计划有没有可行性
Let's see if the plan has legs.
你们要做好各自的部分
Gonna need you guys to do your part.
我行程表上周四还空着 所以
Yeah, I got an opening in my schedule on Thursday, so...
就得是今晚
It's gotta be tonight.
-莲要办个派对 -看来 你得错过了呗
- Renn's throwing a party. - Well, you're missing it.
我很快就会告诉你细节
I'll give you the details in a minute.
你是叫我们走吗
Is that your way of telling us to leave?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
蒲伯有什么的嫌疑 嗑药
Pope suspect anything? Meds?
我不知道
I don't know.
那J呢
What about J?
J什么
他可能对利用尼基她爸有意见
He might have an opinion on using Nicky's dad.
我想让J知道的时候他会知道的
J will find out when I want him to.
好 我们达成一致了
Good. We agree.
不 我们没有
No, we don't agree.
你说的是军事基地啊
You're talking about a military base.
你也是吧 哈
You, too, huh?
目标越大 风险越大
The bigger the score, the bigger the risk.
按我说的做就不会了
But not if we do it my way.
哇 你是我手下败将
Whoo! I'm making you my bitch.
是啊 可巴斯让我们俩做他的手下
Yeah, Baz is making us both his bitches.
如果他的想法能行 至少我们会大赚一把
Well, if his idea works, at least we'll be rolling in it.
就算我们可以抢诺克斯堡［美国肯塔基州军事基地］
You know, we could rob Fort Knox,
小精灵还是会限制我们零用
and Smurf would still have us on allowance.
这他妈太扯淡了
This is bullshit.
我现在本来可以在个嗨趴上
I could be at a killer party right now.
是啊 抢个房子也很酷
Yeah, and robbing a house would be rad
-如果巴斯不让我们做所有的事 -嗯哼
- if Baz doesn't make us do all the work. - Mm-hmm.
怎么了
What's up?
在等小精灵
Just waiting for Smurf.
什么 你要去教堂啊
What, are you going to church?
没 我要和尼基家里人共进晚餐
No. I'm going to dinner with Nicky's family.
如果是她爸付钱 叫只龙虾
Well, if her dad's paying, get the lobster.
你们不是该上路了吗
Shouldn't you boys be getting a move on?
是啊 这局玩好后
Yeah, after this game.
J 能请你去车上等我吗 谢谢
J, can you wait for me in the car, please?
我想你现在就去 并且集中精力
I want you to go now and focus.
听着 如果你觉得我们没能力做这个
Look, if you don't think we're capable
你可以去找别人
of doing this job, you can go find someone else to do it.
宝贝儿 我永远不会强制你做任何
Baby, I would never ask you to do anything
-你不想做的事 -很好
- you feel uncomfortable with. - Good.
那去告诉巴斯我们
- Then tell Baz we're taking
-今晚不干他的破事儿了
-the night off from his bullshit.
去啊
Go.
你真的这么想
You really feel that way?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
德兰
Deran?
告诉她 老兄
Tell her, man.
孬种
Pussy!
我觉得蒲伯会很高兴替上你
I think Pope will be happy to fill in for you.
我会记得谁想在我分赃的时候
And I'll remember who pulled their weight
滥竽充数
when I divvy up the take.
凯瑟
- Cath?
Cath.
嘿
Hey.
我们等过你 但是莉娜累了
We waited for you, but Lena was tired.
我在小精灵那耽误了
Yeah, I got held up at Smurf's.
我打过电话
I called.
德兰说你几小时前就走了
Deran said you left hours ago.
你觉得我喜欢这样吗
You think I like this?
做唠叨的妻子 老问你去了哪儿
The nagging wife, always asking where you've been.
你还满擅长的啊
Well, you're getting good at it.
你知道 酒吧里整天有人来勾搭我
You know, guys come into the bar and hit on me all the time.
我没有出轨 凯瑟 好吗
I'm not cheating on you, Cath. Okay?
曾经那很烦人
Used to be a pain in the ass,
试着礼貌地拒绝他们又不会失去小费
trying to let them down gently without losing tips.
现在我倒是期待
Now I look forward to it,
有人想跟我说话
someone wanting to talk to me.
我当时在我爸家
I was at my dad's.
他住在维斯塔那儿一辆房车里
He lives in a trailer over in Vista.
我以为他被判了无期徒刑
I thought he was in for life.
我猜州里觉得26年够了
I guess the state thought 26 years was enough.
你原意跟他说话了吗
You're talking to him?
在他对你做了那些事之后
After everything he did to you...
如果父母还活着
You telling me you wouldn't talk to your parents
你告诉我你不愿意跟他们说话吗
if they were still alive?
小精灵知道吗
Does Smurf know?
不 不 小精灵不知道
No. No, Smurf does not know.
这不重要 他离开了
Doesn't matter anyway. He's gone.
去哪
Where?
谁知道 反正走了
Who knows? But he's gone.
那你干嘛去那儿
Then why'd you go there?
去喂他的猫
Feed his cat.
你 你去喂他的猫
You... You went to feed his cat?
是啊
I did. Yes.
-祝您健康 -祝您健康
- Salud. - Salud.
我不知道夫勒诺斯的货这么棒
I had no idea the shit in Fresno was this good.
你该让你的表兄多来做客
You should have your cousins come down more often.
你还要来一排吗
You ready for another line?
我反正不用再去哪
I don't have to be anywhere.
你知道的 如果你告诉我
You know, if you'd told me
你关店以后是做这些
this is what you do after you close...
-我每个晚上都会来
- I would've been here every night.
斯考特管着这里
- Scottie manages the place.
恩
Mm.
哇哈
Whoa! Whoo!
哇
- Whoo!
现在我要你让我尖叫
Now I want you to make me scream.
恩
Hmm.
好吧
All right.
我不想呆在家
#I don't like staying at home #
当月亮猩红
#When the moon is bleeding red #
醉醺醺在后座从梦中醒来
#Woke up stoned in the backseat from a dream #
梦里我的牙齿从头上脱落
#Where my teeth fell out of my head #
你想放手吗
#Do you feel like letting go? #
过来
Now come here.
我不知道有多远
#I wonder how far down it is #
一切都无趣
#Nothing is fun #
不像从前
#Not like before #
你再也无法使我兴奋
#You don't get me high anymore #
曾经只用一片
#Used to take one #
现在要四片
#Now it takes four #
你再也无法使我兴奋
#You don't get me high anymore #
再也无法使我兴奋
不敢相信小精灵让我做这破事
Can't believe Smurf has me doing this shit.
不是小精灵 是巴斯
It's not Smurf. It's Baz.
我从青春期开始就没抢过房子了
I haven't hit a house since, like, puberty.
上帝啊 老兄 你以前抱怨活太难做
Jeez, man, you were bitching about the job being too hard.
现在你又抱怨活儿太简单
Now you're bitching about it being too easy.
-你到底在这干嘛 -你想一个人做吗
- Why you even here? - Do you wanna do it alone?
-你呢 -放轻松 老兄 别
- Do you? - Relax, man. No.
呆在牢子里一晚上 你就心情不好了
One night in jail and you're in a shitty mood.
今晚有事要发生
Something happens tonight...
我要闪亮登场 你懂我的意思吗
I'm coming out firing. Do you understand me?
他们得杀了我 因为老子才不要回去里边儿
They're gonna have to kill me 'cause I'm not going back inside.
老天 你在里面经历了什么
Jesus, man, what happened to you in there?
在这儿 磁铁
- Bingo. Magnet.
好吧 拿电视
All right, TV.
你说
What do you say
我们去吸点然后再战怎么样
we do some more blow and go again?
-恩 -听上去不错
- Hmm? - Tempting.
但是我必须要走了
But I gotta go.
我不想看到这个
I don't wanna see this.
看到什么
See what?
我被抢的那天 塞奇在波特兰
Sage was in Portland the day I got robbed.
他给我看了机票和所有东西
Showed me a plane ticket and everything.
这是个单纯的误会
It's an easy mistake.
你不必感到难过 我们会找到那个真正的抢劫的人
You don't have to feel bad. We'll find the right guy.
你有我的项链
You had my necklace...
那条你说你从他那里拿回来的项链
the one you said you got from him.
你看着我去死  克雷格
You left me to die, Craig.
我现在要做同样的事情
Now I'm gonna do the same.
啊
Aah!
把这个人渣绑起来
Tie this piece of shit.
－抓住他了吗 -我按住他了 按住他了
- Got it? - I got it, got it.
继续
- Come on.
继续 把他绑好
Come on. Let's get him up.
嗯啊
Uhh!
我在卧室找到了一些珠宝 但是都是次品
I got the jewelry from the bedroom, but it's crap.
连我们买汽油的钱都不够
It won't even cover the cost of gas.
当然啦 谁关心那个 我找到一个公文包
Yeah, who gives a shit? I got the briefcase.
里面有啥
What's in it?
我不知道啊 文件和一些东西
I don't know. Papers and stuff.
文件 巴斯让我们闯进来就是为了一些文件
Papers? Baz has us breaking in for papers?
对啊
Yeah.
你跟我说说为什么我要浪费我的时间
You wanna tell me why I'm wasting my time
来偷一个破电视和破珠宝呢
for a used television and crap jewelry?
听着 我也不知道 我只是按命令行事
Look, I don't know, man. I'm just doing what I'm told.
好吧 我们出去吧
All right, let's get out of here.
快点 快点
Come on, come on.
好的 那么 嗯 两个草莓味的
Okay, so, uh, two strawberries,
一个奶油曲奇味的 妮基 我知道你要薄荷巧克力碎味的 J 你呢
a cookies and cream. Nicky, I know you want mint chip. J?
-巧克力味的 谢谢 -和巧克力味的
- Chocolate, please. - And chocolate.
他太差劲了
This is so lame.
-他很好 一直很亲切 -好吧 所以多少钱
- He's fine. He's being nice. - Okay, so that's...
-额 保罗 -5美元
- Uh, Paul. - That's $5.
-别 别 别 你的钱在这儿不好使 -不 不 别这样 我
- No, no, no. Your money's no good here. - No, no, come on, I...
不用 不用 不用了 你舅舅今天中午请我吃饭了
No, no, no. Your uncle bought me lunch today.
今晚算我账上 好吗 巴斯 他对我很照顾
Tonight is on me. Okay? Baz. He took care of me.
谢谢你 不要了 你们留着找零吧 非常感谢你们
Thank you. No, you guys keep the change. Thank you so much.
我们是有多无聊啊
How boring are we?
对吧
Right?
哦
Oh.
是我
Yeah?
谢谢
Thank you.
我们必须走了
We gotta go.
不 我们现在就走
No, we gotta go right now.
那是白粉吗
That H?
40刀
Four dimes.
能让一头大象吸毒过量
Enough to OD an elephant.
你们不会认为我在买这个吧 啊
You guys don't think I'm buying this, do you?
哈
Huh?
把塑料袋拿过来
Get the plastic.
好的 拿塑料袋
Sure, get the plastic.
好主意啊 嗯哼
Good idea. Mm-hmm.
好 好 我知道现在的情况 好吗
Okay. Okay, l-look... m-message received, okay?
我是个混蛋 所以要打就痛痛快快的打我
I was an asshole. So give me a good beating,
然后我们就扯平了 好吗
and we'll call it even, okay?
我们要把他的尸体扔到哪里
Where do we dump his body?
喂鲨鱼
Arrowhead?
听着 那不是我的错 好吗 我
Look, it wasn't my fault, okay? I...
我 我看了莲的  我看了莲的 我看了她的脉搏
I-I checked Renn's... I checked her... I checked her pulse.
我又不是圣人医生
I'm not a goddamn doctor.
等等 等等  等等
Wait. Wait. Wait, wait! Wait, wait, wait!
你知不知道我的家族 啊
Do you know who my family is? Huh?
如果你对我做了什么 你就开了你自己
If you do anything to me, you're signing your own...
你就是给你自己开了死亡证明
You are signing your own death certificate!
不 不
No! No!
不要 打911 不要 不要 不要
No, call 9-1-1! No, no, no!
别这样 不要 不要让我死 求你
Come on, don't... don't let me die! Please!
你觉得莲当时是什么感受  畜生
How do you think Renn felt, shithead?
求你 做点什么吧 求你了
Please, do... do something! Please!
看看他 他在尿裤子了
Check it out, he's pissing himself.
－噢 狗屎 兄弟
- Oh, shit, man.
喔
Ooh.
生理盐水 就是盐和水
Saline. Salt and water.
一点茶添颜色而已
A little tea for coloring.
喔
Whoo.
那些你从莲那里拿的东西 你还欠着钱
You still owe Renn for what you took.
6千美元 加上今晚800美元的可卡因
6 grand plus $800 for the coke tonight.
拿出来 我们就不杀你 知道了吗
Get it here, we'll let you live, okay?
打个电话
Make a call.
他们到底是怎么闯进来的
How did they break in exactly?
他们说他们是从后门进来的
They said they came in through the back door.
他们打碎了其中一块玻璃 我一直担心
They broke one of those glasses. I always worried...
-噢 -噢 我的天
- Oh. - Oh, my God.
噢 -他们拿走了电脑
Oh! - They got the computer!
哦 我的天 -他们拿走了电视机
Oh, my God. - They took the television.
所有东西都
Everything is...
-哦 我的天 -我真不敢相信
- Oh, my God. - I don't believe it.
警察 他们是从 他们是怎么进来的
Officer, they came in through... How did they come in?
不 不 不是我的公文包
No. No, not my briefcase.
你告诉我他们没有拿走我的公文包
Please tell me they did not take my briefcase.
哦 我的天 我要去楼上看看
Oh, my God. I'm gonna check upstairs,
看看他们拿走了什么 -找我的公文包
- see if they took anything. - Look for my briefcase!
好的 亲爱的 噢 我的天 保罗
Okay, Sweetie. Oh, my God! Paul!
检查我的房间
Check my room!
-我是为了克雷格来的 -你是谁
- I'm here for Craig. - Who are you?
他妈妈
His mother.
你给你妈打电话
You called your mom?
你做了什么 宝贝
What'd you do, Baby?
欺骗我们堂姐 还不管她的死活
Ripped off our cousin and left her to die.
克雷格
Craig?
谢谢
Thank you.
噢 狗屎
Oh, shit.
把衣服穿好 宝贝
Go get dressed, Baby.
你可以把枪拿开 蠢货
You can put your gun away, pendejo.
没有人在这里用枪
Nobody's shootin' anybody here.
他开头的 我们只是跟着做而已
He started it. We just made it right.
所以我们扯平了
So we're even?
并没有
No.
克雷格 把你的钥匙给我
Craig, give me your keys.
钥匙
Your keys.
那是我的杜卡迪车
That's my Ducati.
你在干什么 不要把我的自行车给他
What are you doing? Don't give him my bike.
做错了事 你的东西被没收了
Misbehave, you lose your toys.
到车里去
Go get in the car.
不要因为我的慷慨认为我是个软柿子
Don't you mistake my generosity for weakness.
拿好你的衣服
Got your shirt.
谢谢
Thanks.
有没有 额
Did, um...
你有抢劫妮基的家吗
did you rob Nicky's house?
我听到你跟克雷格有说到这个 那是妮基的吗
I heard you and Craig talking about it. Was it Nicky's?
所以如果是的话怎么样
So what if it was?
你可以抢劫任何人 舅舅
You could've robbed anybody, man.
听着 兄弟 我只是随便说说 好吗
Look, man, I'm just the grunt, okay?
你去问巴斯 他是这个计划的大老板
Talk to Baz. He's the big man with the plan.
他不会这么对他们的
He's not done with them.
先是蒲伯 现在是你
First Pope, now you?
你知道我还曾希望有一天你们这些孩子可以知道
You know I had hoped that someday you boys would know
怎么照顾你们自己
how to take care of yourselves.
你从来都不站在我的立场上
You haven't even heard my side.
我知道你的立场 亲爱的 发自内心地知道
I know your side, Sweetie, by heart.
我鼓励你野性一点  但是要有限度
I encouraged you to be wild, but there's a line.
你期望什么
What do you expect?
你给我的都是些烂工作
All you give me are the shit jobs.
这不是真的
That's not true.
你认为我很傻是吗
You think I'm stupid?
你都没有试着隐藏一下
You don't even try to hide it.
我不认为你很蠢
I don't think you're stupid.
我认为你有真正的天赋
I think you've got real gifts.
是吗 是什么
Yeah? What?
你无所畏惧
You're fearless.
因此你可以做到你兄弟们做不到的事情
You've got what it takes to do things your brothers won't.
他们做不到
They can't.
但是下次像这样的事情发生的时候
But the next time something like this happens,
你不要打电话找我
don't you call me,
因为我不会来的
because I will not come.
想喝一些药水吗
Want some syrup?
给你 只能喝一点点
Here we go. Just a little bit.
正好吗 还是多一些
Good? More?
多一些 哦 我的天
More? Oh, my God.
你会蹦到墙上去的 丫头
You're gonna be bouncing off the walls, kiddo.
呀
Yikes.
-我们应该经常这么做 -对啊
- We should do this more often. - Yeah.
每天都要一份煎饼 记得吗
Pancakes every day. Remember?
我当然记得
I do remember.
我们是小孩子的时候定下来的
We were kids when we agreed to that.
约定就是约定
- A deal's a deal.
那是我们觉得唯一会像真正的父母做的事情
That's only 'cause we thought that's what real parents did.
什么是真正的父母
What's real parents?
一些我跟她之间肯定没有的东西
Something me and her sure as hell didn't have.
-巴斯 -什么 她应该知道
- Baz... - What? She should know
她从哪里来的
where she came from.
你记得其它我们达成统一的事情吗
You remember what else we agreed to?
-没有 -嗯 哼
- No? - Mnh-mnh.
一个女孩 一个男孩
One girl, one boy.
我们负担不起另外一个孩子
We can't afford another kid.
好吧 我正在努力赚钱
Well, I'm workin 'on that.
你说你做完这份工作后
What do you say after this next job,
我们一起去爬山
we take off to the mountains?
像以前那样找一个小屋
Get a cabin like we used to?
你怎么说 莉娜 你想要一个弟弟吗
What do you say, Lena? You want a baby brother?
你想要对吧 看 她想要弟弟
You do? See, she does.
哦 保证是个男孩这有点难啊
Oh, it's kinda hard to guarantee a boy.
决定了就是决定了
Deal's a deal.
好了 我要走了
All right, I gotta split.
拜拜
Bye.
工作开心 爸比
Have a good day at work, Daddy.
-拜 -拜
- Bye. - Bye.
嘿 我带了泳衣过来
Hey. I brought my bikini.
妮基 我觉得我们不该再见面了
Nicky, I don't think we should see each other anymore.
库珀斯说我们能找回来
Cops said there isn't much
我们东西的几率并不大 谢谢你
chance of getting our stuff back. Thanks a lot.
觉得小精灵会给我做一杯血腥玛丽吗
Think Smurf can make me a Bloody Mary?
我是说真的
I mean it.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
对不起
I'm sorry.
等等 你是 你是在跟我分手吗
Wait, you're... you're breaking up with me?
但是你爱我
But you like me.
-我做错了什么 -没有 没有
- Did I do something? - No. No.
那是你有别人了吗 还是什么 你说啊
Is there some other girl? What? Say something.
妮基 你必须走了
Nicky, you have to go.
听着 我知道你很难过
Look, I know it's been hard for you...
-你必须走了 -嘿 你要跟我分手吗
- You have to go. - Hey, you walk away from me?
嘿 这都是胡说
Hey, this is bullshit!
你刚刚跟我家人一起出去吃晚饭
You just went out to dinner with my family.
不是吗 晚餐 冰淇淋
Is that it? Dinner? Ice cream?
这些对你来说太普通了吗
Things get a little too normal for you?
-那有寓意吗 -你以为的平常是
- What's that supposed to mean? - Your idea of normal
看着不认识的人把一根针捅进你妈的身体
was watching some random guy stick a needle in your mom
然后又上了她
before he put his dick inside her.
-别说我妈的坏话
- Don't say shit about my mom.
你不知道发生了什么
You don't know what's going on here.
你什么都不懂
You have no idea.
你干嘛这样
Why are you acting like this?
-别 -为什么
- No. - Why?
听着
Look...
我们之间结束了
it's over.
你离我远点
I want you to stay away from me,
离我家人远点
and you stay away from my family.
吃午饭啦
Lunch!
嘿 老兄 昨晚怎么样 嗨吗
Hey, buddy. How was last night? A rager?
-啥 -莲的派对
- What? - Renn's party.
一般般
It was okay.
照你的描述看 我还以为会很嗨
By the way you made it sound, I thought you'd still be high.
-你在外边建什么
- What are you building out there?
一座喷泉
A fountain.
什么 给谁的 像是 鸟吗
What? For, like, birds?
是给 比如 我啊
For, like, me.
拿着 宝贝儿 你最喜欢的口味
Here you go, Sweetie. It's your favorite.
香辣的
Spicy chili.
-克雷格的看起来好吃 -想干嘛啊 老兄
- Craig's looks good. - What the hell, man?
-吃我的吧 -我不想要你的
- Just take mine. - I don't want yours.
别小题大做
Don't make a big deal about this.
噢 我的老天 如果能让你们闭嘴
Oh, my God. If it get you guys to shut up,
-我要吃你的 -好吧
- I'll have yours. - Fine.
你饿了吗 宝贝儿
You hungry, Sweetie?
怎么了 宝贝儿
What's the matter, honey?
尼基和我分手了
Nicky broke up with me.
你知道原因吗
Do you know why?
哇哦 你没在开玩笑 这真好吃
Wow, you weren't kidding. This stuff is really good.
-是啊 味道很好 -18年陈酿
- Yeah, it's great. - Aged 18 years.
我听过事情全貌了 我觉得你是该喝一杯
After I heard what happened, I figured you could use a drink.
-这你敢信 -不敢
- Can you believe it? - I can't.
条子说是一群外行干的
Cops said that a bunch of amateurs did this.
-是啊 -他们还是查不到啥
- Yeah. - They still have nothing to go off of.
－你有保险吗 －有
- You have insurance? - Yeah.
嗯 这太糟糕了
Yeah. That sucks.
只是一些东西 对吗 都可以买新的
It's just stuff, though, right? It's replaceable.
他们拿了我的公文包
They took my briefcase.
-为什么 -那上了锁
- Why? - It was locked.
他们大概觉得里面有值钱的东西
They probably thought there was something valuable inside?
我 我 我不知道
I-I-I don't know.
但只是工作上的东西 对吗 我说...
But it's just work stuff, right? I mean...
有什么问题吗
What's the problem?
里面有些机密文件
Some of those files are classified.
好吧 它们本来不该拿出基地的
Okay, they're not supposed to be off the base.
我是说 我时不时带它们回家是因为
I mean, I bring them home sometimes because
我不想一辈子呆在该死的办公室
I'd spend the rest of my life in that freaking office.
-我懂 我明白了
- I know. I hear ya.
海军处理这种屁事都很严肃
The Navy takes this shit so seriously.
等等 他们会开了你吗
Wait. Would they fire you?
-他们会在军事法庭审判我 -噢 该死
- They could court-martial me. - Oh, shit.
你有多想要回这些文件
How bad do you want those files back?
这是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
嗯 我们管着一堆低收入资产
Well, we handle a bunch of low income properties,
还跟很多坏家伙打交道
and we deal with some pretty shady characters.
如果我们想解决问题
If we want a problem fixed...
就打电话叫人
we call some guys.
哪种人
What kind of guys?
那种可以到处问的人
The kind of guys that can ask around.
他们可以查出哪组人下的手
They can find out which crew did your house.
也许能把你的箱子拿回来
Maybe get your briefcase back.
他们要怎么做到啊
How are they gonna do that?
别问问题比较好
It's better not to ask questions.
算了 我就不该提
Forget it. I shouldn't have brought it up.
别别别别
No. No, no, no.
给你的人打电话
Call your guys.
好的
Okay.
-嗨 -你在这干嘛
- Hey. - What are you doing here?
我只是在和你爸喝酒
I was just having a drink with your dad.
别让J知道我看到你了 他可能也会对你发脾气
Don't tell J I saw you. He might go off on you, too.
这话什么意思
What does that mean?
他是个狗屎的意思
He's a shit is what it means.
他刚和我分手
He just broke up with me.
-为什么 -我怎么知道
- Why? - Like I know?
一切都正常 然后突然
Everything was cool, and then out of nowhere,
他就翻脸不想跟我在一起了
he just flips out and wants nothing to do with me.
我就该给他一拳
I should've punched him.
要我说 他犯了个大错
Well, he made a big mistake.
-嘿 巴斯 -嘿 老兄 你有空吗
- Hey, Baz. - Hey, man, you free?
想一起喝瓶酒吗
Do you wanna grab a beer?
呃 好 当然 在哪
Uh, yeah. Yeah, sure. Where?
九号塔那怎么样 半小时后见
How about Tower 9? Say half an hour?
-好吧 -很好 待会见
- Okay, cool. - All right, great, I'll see you there.
好 再见
Right, yeah. Okay, bye.
你有看见那个金刚石刀片吗
Have you seen the diamond blade?
我一直往你食物里放这些
I've been putting these in your food
因为你有需要而且从来不听我说
because you need them and you never would've listened to me,
在那个状态你就不会听
not in the state you were in.
所以我该谢谢你
So I should thank you.
说明在标签上
The instructions are on the labels.
你知道你这样会把我送回监狱的
You know you could've gotten me sent back to prison.
你下一次尿检之前
Before your next piss test,
你去告诉你的假释官你又有服药了
you tell your parole officer you're back on your meds.
你凭什么觉得我会吃药
And what makes you think I'm gonna keep taking 'em?
因为你知道你要吃
Because you know you need them.
只有我吃药了你才会喜欢我吗
You don't like me unless I'm on these pills?
是这样吗
Is that it?
-或者我就该冲走它们
- Or I could just flush 'em.
可以吃了也可以冲了
Could take 'em or flush 'em.
这么多选择
So many choices.
嘿 老兄
Hey, man.
嘿
Hey.
我听说尼基的事了
I heard about Nicky.
噢 对 小精灵跟你说的吗
Oh, yeah. Did Smurf tell you?
嗯哼 我以为你俩很好啊
Mm-hmm. I thought things were good.
我这么以为 老兄
Me, too, man.
对她来说不好吧 我猜
Not for her, I guess.
所以她甩了你
So she dumped you?
是啊
Yeah.
我都不知道她要甩我 老兄
I had no idea it was coming, man.
是啊 女人不是总能搞懂的
Yeah, women don't always make sense.
一切都
Thing is...
尼基跟我说你甩了她
Nicky told me you dumped her.
到底哪个是真的 J
So which is it, J?
你别跟我扯淡 我也不跟你扯淡怎么样
How 'bout you don't bullshit me, I don't bullshit you?
你知道最近发生什么了
You figured out what's been going on?
是 知道的够多了
Yeah, enough.
你觉得你在保护她吗
And you think you're protecting her?
-你在利用她 对吗 -是
- You're using her, right? - Yes.
还有她爸
And her dad.
我想到现在为止 你差不多该知道了
I thought you'd know this by now.
所有家庭之外的人就是个旗子 每个都是
Everyone outside the family is a mark. Everyone.
我是个棋子吗
Am I a mark?
听着 你反应过激了 没事的
Look, you overreacted. It's fine.
你还没造成永久的伤害
You didn't do any permanent damage.
但这事是要干的 是吗
But this thing is happening, okay?
你来不来 都要干
With or without you, this is happening.
别把尼基一家拉进来
Just leave Nicky and her family alone.
现在轮到你下命令了吗 你以为事是这么办的吗
Are you making demands now? You think that's how this works?
我们现在只是在谈话 你就很走运了
You're lucky you and I are just talking right now.
你很幸运
You're lucky.
家庭第一 所有别的都是其次
Family comes first. Everything else is second.
你懂吗
You understand me?
我得确认你不会做蠢事
I need to know you're not gonna do anything stupid.
你会做什么蠢事吗 J
Are you gonna do anything stupid, J?
不会的
No.
我想要相信你 真的 我想
I wanna believe you. I really, really do.
家里见
I'll see you back at the house.
我告诉蒲伯药的事了
I told Pope about the medications.
我没得选 但是别担心
I had no choice. And don't worry.
我没和他说你知道这一切
I didn't tell him you knew anything.
他在哪
Where is he?
在宾馆房间 希望是这样
In his hotel room, I hope.
我们可能又有个麻烦了
We may have another problem.
尼基的爸爸吗
Nicky's dad?
不 他那进展很顺利
No, that went just like we wanted it to.
是J
J.
嘿 一切都还好吗
Hey. Is everything okay?
我没听到你的消息还在担心呢
I was worried when I didn't hear from you.
对不起 我只是 呃
I'm sorry. I just, um...
嘿 怎 怎么了 出什么事了
Hey, what's... what is it? What's wrong?
我能进来一下吗
Can I come in for a little while?
当然 进来吧
Yeah. Yeah, of course. Come on.